Talk to the Gun is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Justin W. Smith.
Bryce Turner, a former bounty hunter loses everything even his 8 year
old daughter taken by a corrupt and vengful business man.
But nothing will stop him from finding her alive and putting
the pieces of his life back together again.
Bryce Turner, played by Justin W. Smith.
Jessica Banks, played by Sarah Christine.
Carl Hicks, played by Todd Risby.
Rosie Turner, played by Heather Farace.
Det. Orlando McCoy, played by Mauricio Bobino.
Delfino Mason, played by Daniel Valent.
The Naked Gun is a 2025 American action comedy parody film directed by Akiva
Schaffer, who co-wrote the screenplay with Dan Gregor and Doug Mand.
The fourth film in the Naked Gun franchise, it stars Liam Neeson in the main role, with Pamela
Anderson, Paul Walter Hauser, Kevin Durand, and Danny Huston in supporting roles.
Its plot follows the son of Lt.
Frank Drebin who must succeed in his father's footsteps
to prevent the closure of Police Squad.
A fourth Naked Gun film was announced in 2009, as a direct-to-TV sequel starring Leslie Nielsen, with Alan Spencer being
attached to write; however, the project was cancelled due to Spencer's departure, and Nielsen died in November 2010.
After several years of development, including being redeveloped as a reboot starring Ed Helms in 2013, it was announced in
January 2021 that Seth MacFarlane had been hired to develop the project, and he expressed interest in casting Neeson.
Although MacFarlane was hired to direct, Schaffer replaced him after the
film was greenlit in October 2022, and Neeson was cast.
Anderson was cast in April 2024, and further casting took place the
following month, when filming began in Atlanta, Georgia.
Filming wrapped that June.
The Naked Gun premiered at the SVA Theater in Manhattan on July 28, 2025, and was
released in the United States by Paramount Pictures on August 1, 2025.
It received positive reviews from critics and grossed $102.1
million worldwide on a $42 million budget.
The film explores themes of bounty hunter, loss of loved
one, kidnapping, revenge, loss of job.
The tone is intense.